<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.coreasm.eclipse.feature"
      label="CoreASM Eclipse Plugin"
      version="1.1.1.qualifier"
      provider-name="CoreASM Group">

   <description url="https://github.com/CoreASM/coreasm.core">
      The CoreASM Eclipse Plugin
   </description>

   <copyright url="https://github.com/CoreASM/coreasm.core">
      The CoreASM Modeling Framework
CoreASM is an open source project that focuses on offering a lean executable ASM (Abstract State Machines) language, in combination with a supporting tool environment for high-level design, experimental validation and formal verification (where appropriate) of abstract system models.
CoreASM offers a rich ASM language with a formally defined semantics that is faithful to the original semantics of ASM and is the first ASM tool that explicitly supports distributed ASM computation models with custom scheduling policies. The extensibility of its language and modeling environment, the most significant feature of CoreASM, provides utmost flexibility for extending its language definition and execution engine in order to tailor it to the particular needs of virtually any conceivable application context.
CoreASM is one of the few ASM tools that is implemented as an open framework. CoreASM can be used in differnt forms: it offers a modeling framework, it can be viewed as a tool suite with different tools it offers around the engine, while the engine itself can be used as an stand-alone tool (using its command-line or this Eclipse plugin UI).
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.opensource.org/licenses/afl-3.0.php">
      The CoreASM Engine and the CoreASM Eclipse Plugin are licensed under the Academic Free License version 3.0 which is available from either of these web page: http://www.opensource.org/licenses/afl-3.0.php
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="CoreASM Update Site" url="http://pmserver.informatik.uni-ulm.de/coreasm/org.coreasm.eclipse.updatesite/"/>
      <discovery label="CoreASM @ github.com" url="https://github.com/CoreASM/coreasm.core"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.console"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.views"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.coreasm.eclipse"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.1.qualifier"/>

</feature>
